In terms of justice, the ancient Persian Empire could be said to have been harsh, but fair.
在正义方面，古代波斯帝国可以说是严酷而公正的。
The criminal code included the principal of “lex talionis”, an eye for an eye, tooth
刑法中包含“ lex talionis”的原理，以牙还牙，以牙还牙
for a tooth, misdemeanors usually warranted fines, you might be branded for slander, and
对于牙齿，轻罪通常应处以罚款，您可能被冠以诽谤的烙印，并且
for the worst crimes you would get the death penalty.
对于最严重的罪行，您将获得死刑。
On occasions there was a two strikes rule, meaning someone wouldn’t be executed for
有时会有两次罢工规则，这意味着不会为某人执行死刑
their first offense.
他们的第一次进攻。
So, there you are in ancient Persia, two strikes down.
因此，您在古老的波斯那里，遭受了两次打击。
You are wondering how the death penalty will be metered out.
您想知道如何确定死刑。
Will it be suffocation by ashes perhaps, or maybe having molten gold poured down your
会被灰烬窒息窒息，还是将熔化的金倒在您的身上？
throat as what might have happened to the Roman emperor Valerian.
就像罗马皇帝瓦莱里亚人可能发生的一样。
It’s hard to say which would be worse, but today we think have a Persian punishment that
很难说会更糟，但是今天我们认为有一种波斯惩罚措施
was the most brutal of them all.
是其中最残酷的。
While the ancient Persians did have strict laws pertaining to matters of justice, as
虽然古代波斯人确实有关于正义的严格法律，
we said, that didn’t at times stop them from being tremendously brutal.
我们说过，这有时并不能阻止他们变得如此残酷。
We’ll give you a few more examples before we get to possibly the worst punishment of
在给您带来最严重的惩罚之前，我们将再举几个例子。
them all.
商场。
Take for example the death of a Persian judge called Sisamnes.
例如，一位波斯法官Sisamnes的去世。
It’s said that he was corrupt and King Cambyses II of Persia who ruled from 530 BC to 522
据说他是腐败的，波斯国王坎比西斯二世统治于公元前530年至522年
BC wanted to make an example out of him as a warning to others who might think about
BC希望以他为榜样，以警告其他可能考虑的人
corrupting the courts.
破坏法院。
It’s said the judge was flayed from head to toe and then his skin was used to make
据说法官从头到脚被剥皮，然后用他的皮肤
a chair.
一把椅子。
As the tale goes, anyone appointed from then on as a judge would have to spend some time
随着故事的发展，从那时起任命的任何人都将不得不花费一些时间
sitting in that chair so they would know what would happen if they were corrupt.
坐在那把椅子上，这样他们就会知道如果他们腐败了会发生什么。
You can see this horrific spectacle in the paintings “The Arrest of Sisamnes” and
您可以在“ Sisamnes的逮捕”画中看到这种可怕的景象。
“Flaying of Sisamnes.”
“ Sisamnes的铺面。”
Then there’s the story of Cyrus the Great.
然后是居鲁士大帝的故事。
It’s written that his wife became quite unhappy with one of her eunuchs.
据记载，他的妻子对她的一位太监感到非常不满。
So unhappy in fact, that she ordered that he be killed three times.
事实上，她非常不高兴，下令将他杀死3次。
This is called The Triple Death.
这称为三重死亡。
It’s said first his eyes were pulled from his head, but then he was nursed back to health.
据说首先他的眼睛从头上移开，然后又被调养。
His second death was being flayed, but again he was nursed so he wouldn’t die.
他的第二次死亡被剥夺了，但是他又得到了护理，所以他不会死。
We imagine he couldn’t have been completely flayed as that resulted in certain death.
我们想象他不可能被完全剥皮，因为那会导致某些死亡。
When he was better he was then crucified and the job was done.
当他好一些时，他被钉在十字架上，工作完成了。
We should say, however, that there are many versions of this tale.
但是，我们应该说这个故事有很多版本。
We’ll stick with this one for now.
现在，我们将坚持使用这一模式。
So, with these two executions in mind, could there really be anything worse?
因此，考虑到这两次处决，真的会有更糟的事情吗？
Well, now we have to look at the story of a man called Mithridates.
好了，现在我们必须看一个叫做Mithridates的男人的故事。
He was a young Persian soldier who was put to death in 401BC.
他是年轻的波斯士兵，于401BC被处死。
It’s said this man accidentally killed Cyrus the Younger, the rebel who was intending to
据说这个人不小心杀死了打算叛逆的叛逆者赛勒斯（Cyrus the Younger）
kill his older brother Arsaces so he could inherit the throne.
杀死他的哥哥阿尔萨斯，以便他可以继承王位。
Thousands of men were behind Cyrus and this culminated in the Battle of Cunaxa.
成千上万的人落后于居鲁士（Cyrus），并在库纳沙（Cunaxa）战役中达到顶峰。
Cyrus’ army got the upper hand after charging Artaxerxes' army, all was going well, the
赛勒斯的军队在向Artaxerxes的军队冲锋之后占据了上风，一切进展顺利，
throne was in his sights.
王位在他眼前。
Cyrus then went to attack his brother’s personal bodyguard and then…oops…out of
居鲁士然后去攻击他哥哥的私人保镖，然后……哎呀……走出
nowhere a javelin just hit him and killed him on the spot.
无处标枪击中他并当场杀死他。
This was a huge setback for the rebels and they all retreated.
这对叛军来说是巨大的挫折，他们全都撤退了。
Their future king was dead, it was over.
他们未来的国王已经死了，一切都结束了。
We know this because the story was recorded by the Greek biographer Plutarch in his essay
我们知道这一点是因为这个故事是由希腊传记作家普鲁塔克（Plutarch）在他的论文中记录的
the “Life of Artaxerxes.”
“ Artaxerxes的生活”。
Another Greek writer called Ctesias told Plutarch of the fate of the man that accidentally killed
另一位叫Ctesias的希腊作家告诉Plutarch这个被意外杀害的人的命运
Cyrus with that javelin.
赛勒斯和那个标枪。
As you know, his name was Mithridates.
如您所知，他的名字叫Mithridates。
It’s understandable perhaps that some people were perhaps a bit miffed with Mithridates.
也许有些人对Mithridates感到有些厌恶，这是可以理解的。
Only the severest of punishments would do, and that’s where scaphism comes in.
只有最严厉的惩罚才能奏效，这就是船长主义的根源。
This is how Plutarch describes this very unusual kind of death penalty.
这就是Plutarch如何描述这种非常不寻常的死刑。
We will paraphrase as his  is a bit dated now.
由于他的语言有些过时，我们将予以解释。
So, two boats of equal size were put on top of each other and nailed together.
因此，将两艘大小相等的船彼此叠放并钉在一起。
It kind of made a floating coffin.
它有点像一个浮动的棺材。
Holes were made in the boats so that the prisoner could be fastened in the them but with his
在船上打了个洞，以便囚犯可以被固定在船上，但是
hands, feet and head sticking out.
手，脚和头部伸出。
So far so good.
到现在为止还挺好。
He was floating, his head was protruding, he was getting rather hot.
他在浮动，头在伸出，变得越来越热。
He was left there with the hot sun shining on his face.
他被灼热的阳光照在脸上。
His body was baking hot inside the floating tomb.
他的尸体在漂浮的坟墓中炙热。
They then force fed Mithridates milk and honey, and in good size portions, too.
然后，他们也强制喂食Mithridates牛奶和蜂蜜，并按适量的份量喂食。
They also covered his face with the stuff.
他们还用这些东西遮住了他的脸。
Soon his honey-covered face was covered with flies that were feasting on him and the honey.
很快，他的蜂蜜覆盖的脸被苍蝇覆盖，这些苍蝇在他和蜂蜜上大吃一顿。
He was then force fed more and more until his belly was distended and he had produced
然后，他越来越被迫吃饱，直到他的腹部张开并且他产生了
quite the pile of excrement.
大量的排泄物。
At this point, as Plutarch said, “creeping things and vermin spring out of the corruption
正如Plutarch所说，“在这一点上，腐败不断蔓延，害虫滋生
and rottenness of the excrement.”
和排泄物的烂烂。”
These things entered Mithridates’ bowels, while his flesh was slowly being eaten too
这些东西进入了Mithridates的肠子，而他的肉也被慢慢吃掉了
from the outside.
从外部。
This slow devouring by insects and vermin it’s said lasted 17 days.
据说这种缓慢吞噬昆虫和害虫的行为持续了17天。
At that point, poor, young Mithridates with the bad javelin shot was eaten alive.
到那时，活泼的，标枪射击不好的贫穷，年轻的Mithridates被吃掉了。
There was another description of this by a 12th-century Byzantine chronicler called Joannes
十二世纪的拜占庭编年史学家乔安妮斯对此作了另一种描述。
Zonaras.
Zonaras。
It’s really the same story, but he embellished the tale somewhat.
确实是同一故事，但他对这个故事有所修饰。
This is the conclusion, word for word in translation:
这是结论，在翻译中一个字接一个字：
“Flies, wasps, and bees, attracted by the sweetness, settle on his face and all such
“被甜蜜吸引的苍蝇，黄蜂和蜜蜂落在他的脸上，所有这些
parts of him as project outside the boats, and miserably torment and sting the wretched
他的某些部分投射到船外，悲惨地折磨着st琐的人
man.
男人。
Moreover his belly, distended as it is with milk and honey, throws off liquid excrements,
此外，他的腹部因牛奶和蜂蜜的膨胀而散开，排泄了粪便，
and these putrefying breed swarms of worms, intestinal and of all sorts.
这些令人讨厌的品种繁多的蠕虫，肠道和各种各样的蠕虫。
Thus the victim lying in the boats, his flesh rotting away in his own filth and devoured
因此，受害者躺在船上，他的肉腐烂了，吞噬了
by worms, dies a lingering and horrible death.”
被蠕虫杀死，缠绵而可怕的死亡。”
But is that it, just one case of scaphism throughout history?
但是，仅仅是历史上的一种船长主义案件吗？
Well, it seems like the one case everyone talks about is the one we just described,
好吧，似乎每个人都在谈论的一个案例就是我们刚刚描述的一个案例，
although most sources call scaphism an ancient form of punishment as if it happened time
尽管大多数资料都称“ capcaphism”是一种古老的惩罚形式，就像发生时间一样
and again.
然后再次。
We did find an excerpt from a book called “The History of Christian Martyrdom.”
我们确实从《基督教难的历史》一书中摘录。
In that book it’s written that a bishop called Marcus in 363 AD destroyed a pagan
在那本书中写道，公元363年一个叫马库斯（Marcus）的主教摧毁了一个异教徒
temple and then erected a church.
庙，然后建立了一座教堂。
This didn’t go down well with Roman emperor Julian the Apostate.
罗马皇帝朱利安（Julian）背叛的情况并不太好。
It’s written that as punishment he took Marcus and hung him up in a basket and left
据记载，作为惩罚，他将马库斯（Marcus）吊在篮子里然后离开
him there to be feasted on by insects.
他在那里被昆虫盛宴。
But this seems like a case of dying in the hot sun rather than hardcore scaphism.
但这似乎是在烈日下垂死的情况，而不是顽固的船首主义。
There’s actually quite the debate about scaphism on the Wiki Talk page, with some
在Wiki Talk页面上，实际上存在着关于冒牌交易的辩论，其中有些
editors questioning the veracity of Plutarch and asking for other sources.
编辑质疑Plutarch的真实性并要求其他来源。
Plutarch did indeed write that account of scaphism, but some historians believe he may
普鲁塔克确实写了关于船长主义的论述，但一些历史学家认为他可能
have done so to demonize the Persians and make his own culture look better.
这样做是为了妖魔波斯人并使他自己的文化看起来更好。
We will never know exactly what happened to Mithridates, but right now that’s the prevailing
我们永远不会确切地知道Mithridates发生了什么，但是现在这才是流行的
story.
故事。
Perhaps he was the only man ever to get the full dose of scaphism, or maybe old Plutarch
也许他是有史以来唯一获得全部告白主义的人，或者也许是老普鲁塔克（Plutarch）
was an ancient publisher of fake news.
是一个虚假新闻的古老出版商。
So, did we find the worst punishment of all time?
那么，我们是否找到了有史以来最恶劣的惩罚？
Also, check out the brand new channel called “I Am.”
另外，请访问名为“我是”的全新频道。
Real stories come to life as they’re told from the perspective of the people who lived
从生活中的人们的角度讲起，真实的故事栩栩如生
it.
它。
Check out “I Am Vlad the Impaler” right now and be one of the first to subscribe!
立即查看“我是穿刺者弗拉德”，并成为第一个订阅的人之一！